# Caitlin Cassidy

Certified Developer

## Personal Information



c.cassidy2331@gmail.com



(847) 609-6063



Crystal Lake, IL



www.linkedin.com/in/caitlin-cassidy-cc/

#### Skills



# Certifications

Certification	Issued By	Date Earned
Responsive Web Design	freeCodeCamp	January 2022
Responsive Web Design	Sololearn	December 2022
Web Dev Fundamentals	Sololearn	December 2022
The Complete Web Developer in 2023: ZTM	Udemy	January 2023
HTML	Sololearn	December 2022
CSS	Sololearn	December 2022
JavaScript	Sololearn	December 2022
Java	Sololearn	June 2022
SQL	Sololearn	July 2022

# **Profile**

Detail-oriented and task-focused Certified Developer eager to enhance technical skills and apply 8+ years of Operations experience to roles in the Tech Industry. Possesses a genuine passion for creative problemsolving and delivering premium results, as a catalyst to creating an open and collaborative work environment.

# **Work Experience**

#### **♦** Associate Software Engineer

Revature, WA

03/2022 - 01/2023

- Completed three month Full Stack Development training program lead by Revature Training covering databases, front-end and back-end technologies.
- Worked on individual, small team and large team projects responsible for creating, maintaining, and further developing exiting e-commerce applications.
- Coordinated working code and project files with other remote team members via GitHub and coordinates project assignments via shared steam Trello boards.

#### **♦** Executive Assistant/Operations Director

Flying Saucer & Co., IL

01/2020 - 11/2021

- Created a stream-lined and efficient filing system through organizing and logically filing physical and electronic copies of all company documents including invoices, legal documents, equipment specs, etc.
- Developed the structure and organization for the shared company Google Drive hierarchy to document, track and update employee tasks, projects, etc. along with performing ongoing monitoring.
- Created shared Google Sheet to document company social media activity including platform posting, caption information, company partners, tagged artists, related hashtags, along with links to approved photos or videos per posting.

### ◆ Floor/Space Planning Analyst

Walgreens Corporate, IL

06/2018 - 01/2020

- Merchandised average of 3-4 existing and newly remodeled Walgreens retail stores per week to reflect and incorporate corporate dictated design scope utilizing JDA program.
- Quality checked average of 2-3 merchandised stores per week via review and confirmation of correct merchandise flow and adjacencies, fixture properties, floorplan settings, etc.
- Maintained accuracy of floor plan data by raising tickets to address issues with existing floor plans or conflicting fixture information between existing floor plans and D1 Auto CAD drawings

# **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Fine Arts in Interior Design**

Council for Interior Design Accreditation (CIDA)
The Illinois Institute of Art - Schaumburg
2009 - 2012